discountwalas.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - Discountwalas

This policy explains what information we collect when you use discountwalas.com, services, mobile applications, products, and content (“Services”). It also has information about how we store, use, transfer, and delete that information. Our aim is not just to comply with privacy law. It’s to earn your trust.

 **Information We Collect & How We Use It**

discountwalas.com We don’t collect data in order to advertise to you. The tracking we do at discountwalas.com is to make our product work as well as possible.

In order to give you the best possible experience using discountwalas.com, we collect information from your interactions with our network. Some of this information, you actively tell us (such as your email address, which we use to track your account or communicate with you). Other information, we collect based on actions you take while using discountwalas.com, such as what pages you access and your interactions with our product features (like highlights, follows, and applause). This information includes records of those interactions, your Internet Protocol address, information about your device (such as device or browser type), and referral information.

We use this information to:

  * provide, test, improve, promote and personalize our Services
  * fight spam and other forms of abuse
  * generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how people use our Services

When you create your discountwalas.com account, and authenticate with a third-party service (like Twitter, Facebook or Google) we may collect, store, and periodically update information associated with that third-party account, such as your lists of friends or followers. We will never publish through your third-party account without your permission.

 **Information Disclosure**

discountwalas.com won’t transfer information about you to third parties for the purpose of providing or facilitating third-party advertising to you. We won’t sell information about you. We will object to requests for information about users of our services that we believe are improper.

 **Data Storage**

discountwalas.com uses third-party vendors and hosting partners, such as Amazon, for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology we need to run discountwalas.com. We maintain two types of logs: server logs and event logs.

 **Tracking & Cookies**

We use browser cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you return to our Services. We use them in various ways, for example to log you in, remember your preferences (such as default language), evaluate email effectiveness, allow our paywall and meter to function, and personalize content and other information.

discountwalas.com doesn’t track you across the Internet. We track only your interactions within the our network.

Some third-party services that we use to provide the discountwalas.com Service, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), may place their own cookies in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by discountwalas.com only and not the use of cookies by third parties.

 **Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Information**

If you have a discountwalas.com account, you can access, modify or export your personal information, or delete your account [here](https://www.discountwalas.com/edit-profile/).

To protect information from accidental or malicious destruction, we may maintain residual copies for a brief time period. But, if you delete your account, your information and content will be unrecoverable after that time.

 **Data Security**

We use encryption (HTTPS/TLS) to protect data transmitted to and from our site. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, so we can’t guarantee security. You use the Service at your own risk, and you’re responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account.

 **Business Transfers**

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, reorganization or sale of assets such that your information would be transferred or become subject to a different privacy policy, we’ll notify you in advance so you can opt out of any such new policy by deleting your account before transfer.

 **Email from  discountwalas.com**

Sometimes we’ll send you emails about your account, service changes or new policies. You can’t opt out of this type of “transactional” email (unless you delete your account). But you can opt out of non-administrative emails such as digests, newsletters, and activity notifications through your account.

When you interact with an email sent from discountwalas.com (such as opening an email or clicking on a particular link in an email), we may receive information about that interaction. We won’t email you to ask for your password or other account information. If you receive such an email, please send it to us so we can investigate.

 **Description of Processing Activity**

discountwalas.com collects and stores personal information about its users to customize their reading experience and enable personalized distribution of content. It shares minimal data with its service providers.

 **Purposes of Processing**

  * Provide, test, promote, and improve the services
  * Gather usage statistics of services
  * Provide customized reading experience
  * Publish and distribute user-generated content
  * Provide access to paid content
  * Fight spam, fraud, and other abuse of services

 **Categories of Personal Data Collected**

  * Username
  * Display name
  * Bio
  * Avatar image
  * Email address (non-public)
  * Session activity (security)
  * Linked social media accounts (optional)
  * IP address
  * Browser information
  * Reading history (on com network only)
  * Network interactions (recommends, follows, etc.)
  * Posts, responses, or series published by user

 **Categories of Recipients**

discountwalas.com shares minimal personal data with third-party processors in order to provide the Services. These processors offer at least the same level of data protection as that set out in this statement. This includes the following categories of recipients:

  * Hosting, Storage, & Other Infrastructure
  * Security
  * Analytics
  * Communication & Support
  * Payment Processors

Search engines will index user profiles, public interactions, and any user-generated content. Users may also share links to your content on social media.

 **Embedded Content**

discountwalas.com posts may contain third-party embeds, which may in some cases collect and store personal data. The use of personal data by embedded content providers is not covered by this statement, but by the privacy policies of those sites or services.

 **Existence of Automated Decision-making**

discountwalas.com collects and stores personal data about its users to customize reading. This includes automated decision-making to promote content tailored to the preferences and interests indicated by the user, and to their browsing history and network interactions.

discountwalas.com also filters content for the purposes of fighting and preventing spam, fraud, and other forms of abuse.

 **Retention**

discountwalas.com retains personal data associated with your account for the lifetime of your account. If you would like to delete your personal information, you can delete your account at any time. Deleted account profile pages will yield an error 404 “file not found” page, immediately upon initiating deletion, and will become unrecoverable in our system after a period of fourteen days. It may take several additional days for your personal data to be de-indexed from search engines, depending on those search engines’ practices, over which discountwalas.com may have limited or no control.

 **Google Login**  
1\. Discountwalas  
In order to provide a customized user experience with regards deals, discounts and product purchases across e-commerce platforms, we would be requiring support of the Gmail API. We intend to provide e-mail support to users to aggregate their online purchases, which would involve use of features like mail merge, package delivery updates, etc.  
Keeping such mails away from the Spam folder would be of utmost importance. We would be explaining our users the need for their Gmail account access to ensure that our mails are never deleted by mistake or are never left unread if they land in their spam folder.

2\. We have multiple websites ranging from Business News, Motivational website, Latest coupon deals, Astrology etc. which makes social profiling of our user base extremely important. Separate authentication shall be done for each website post which information can be personalized to create a custom user experience.

Through these multiple websites there would be significant interchange of data between Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Drive, Google Analytics and Youtube for which we intend to develop a CRM tool.

Since all websites will have an interconnected user base, keeping them logged in though a single Gmail login would immensely help us. We would be explaining our users the need for their Gmail account access to ensure that our mails are never deleted by mistake or are never left unread if they land in their spam folder.
